const questions = [
    {
      question: "1 : What is the capital of France?",
      options: ["Berlin", "Madrid", "Paris", "Lisbon"],
      answer: "Paris"
    },
    {
      question: "2 : Which planet is known as the Red Planet?",
      options: ["Earth", "Mars", "Jupiter", "Saturn"],
      answer: "Mars"
    },
    {
      question: "3 : Who wrote 'Hamlet'?",
      options: ["Charles Dickens", "Mark Twain", "William Shakespeare", "J.K. Rowling"],
      answer: "William Shakespeare"
    },
    {
      question: "4 : Who wrote 'Romeo and Juliet'?",
      options: ["William Shakespeare", "Charles Dickens", "Leo Tolstoy", "Mark Twain"],
      answer: "William Shakespeare"
    },
    {
      question: "5 : What is the largest mammal in the world?",
      options: ["Elephant", "Blue Whale", "Giraffe", "Great White Shark"],
      answer: "Blue Whale"
    },
    {
      question: "6 : In which year did the Titanic sink?",
      options: ["1905", "1912", "1920", "1935"],
      answer: "1912"
    },
    {
      question: "7 : What is the chemical symbol for water?",
      options: ["H2O", "O2", "CO2", "H2"],
      answer: "H2O"
    },
    {
      question: "8 : Which continent is the Sahara Desert located on?",
      options: ["Asia", "Africa", "South America", "Australia"],
      answer: "Africa"
    },
    {
      question: "9 : Who painted the Mona Lisa?",
      options: ["Leonardo da Vinci", "Vincent van Gogh", "Pablo Picasso", "Claude Monet"],
      answer: "Leonardo da Vinci"
    },
    {
      question: "10 : How many colors are there in a rainbow?",
      options: ["5", "6", "7", "8"],
      answer: "7"
    },
    {
      question: "11 : What is the smallest prime number?",
      options: ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
      answer: "2"
    },
    {
      question: "12 : Which is the longest river in the world?",
      options: ["Amazon River", "Nile River", "Yangtze River", "Mississippi River"],
      answer: "Nile River"
    },
    {
      question: "13 : What is the capital of Japan?",
      options: ["Beijing", "Seoul", "Tokyo", "Bangkok"],
      answer: "Tokyo"
    },
    {
      question: "14 : Which gas do plants primarily use for photosynthesis?",
      options: ["Carbon Dioxide","Oxygen", "Nitrogen", "Hydrogen"],
      answer: "Carbon Dioxide"
    },
    {
      question: "15 : Who is known as the father of computers?",
      options: ["Alan Turing", "Thomas Edison", "Nikola Tesla","Charles Babbage"],
      answer: "Charles Babbage"
    }
    // Add more questions as needed
  ];

  export default questions;